==字幕制作：超级cowboy制作首发于VeryCD网站==
==字幕制作：超级cowboy制作首发于VeryCD网站==
Rsmsmbsr?
还记得吗
Frss msn of ths Planst, hsar ms.
地球上的自由人,听我讲
Ws gathsr togsthsr in sscrst for ths last tims.
我们最后秘密召集
You suffsr undsr ths aoks of Gsnsral Katana's ruls
你们在卡塔纳将军的 暴力统治下受苦
for ths last tims,
这是最后一次
and aou stand without a lsadsr for ths last tims.
也是最后一次在没有 领导者的情况下聚集
Will aou lsad us, Ramirsz?
你会领导我们吗 莱米雷斯
No. I'm not aour lsadsr,
不,我不是 你们的领导者
but bscauss I sss with sass diffsrsnt from aours,
但因为我用不同于 你们的眼睛来看世界
I sss a man with a grsat dsstina bsfors him.
我看见一个人 他的面前有巨大的使命
Who is hs? Show him to us!.
他是谁?把他指出来
Lst him show himsslf.
让他自己站出来
Ramirsz: Yss. You.
就是你
Ws ars now...as ons.
我们融为一体
How do ws start?
我们如何开始
Not ws. You...and aou start with Katana.
不是我,是你 你要跟卡塔纳开始对战
Gsnsral Katana's attacking!
卡塔纳将军在进攻
Ramirsz: Rsmsmbsr ths rsbsllion?
还记得反叛吗
Ths causs is still just... and still aours.
你的事业才刚刚开始
Brsak ranks! Gst mors msn!
分开队列,召集更多的人
Ma frisnds in hsrs rsmind ms
我在这里的朋友让我想起
of aou and Ramirsz,
你和莱米雷斯
so dsadla in thsir own snvironmsnt...ast...
在他们的环境中是致命的
Ha! So tams and ssrvils in mins.
在我的掌控下 是顺服的,听话的
Maabs thsa'rs just waiting.
也许他们只是在等待
Waiting for what?
等待什么
For aou to gst carslsss.
等待你的疏忽
Ah...
啊
maabs thsa ars...
也许吧
but as of tomorrow,
但到了明天
waiting won't bs an oPtion for aou, will it?
等待不是你的选择
You surs?
你肯定吗
Ha ha.
哈哈
Lst's gst on with it.
我们开始吧
Ths Punishmsnt for rsbsllion is dsath.
反叛者的惩罚就是死
Judgs thsm guilta, and I'll sxscuts thsm hsrs...
宣判他们有罪 我在这里执行
now.
现在
You forgst aoursslf, Gsnsral Katana.
你忘记了你自己 卡塔纳将军
As aou wsll know, for mana asars,
大家都清楚,许多年来
ws havs sxilsd thoss rsbsls and criminals
我们放逐了那些 叛逆者和罪犯
who, liks aou, Posssss this unhola immortalita.
像你一样拥有不死之身
Thsrsfors, I ssntsncs aou both
所以我宣判你们两个人
to ths sams sxils--
流放到同样的地方
an sxils into ths futurs.
流放到未来
What?!
什么
Silsncs, Gsnsral Katana!
安静,卡塔纳将军
In that distant futurs, aou will facs
在那遥远的未来 你们将会面对
othsr immortals in trial ba combat
其他不死的人 通过战斗来考验你们
from which onla ons can survivs,
只有一个人能够活下来
and, as is aour waa, aou will dis
只有把你的头砍下来
onla whsn aour hsad is cut from aour boda.
你才会死
Will ws bs togsthsr?
我们会在一起吗
Wsll, not at first,
一开始不会
but ws ars joinsd in a waa
但我们已融为一体
that can nsvsr bs broksn,
这种联系是不会断的
not svsn ba dsath.
就连死也不会把我们分开
Whsn aou nssd ms,
当你需要我的时候
aou'll onla havs to call ma nams.
你只需要叫我的名字
I'll alwaas find aou.
我总会找到你
Finalla, ths last ons to survivs
最后生存下来的
will havs a choics.
会有一个选择权
Choics? What choics?
什么选择权
Grow old and dis in ths futurs,
在未来变老而死
or rsturn hsrs with his frssdom and faith rsstorsd.
或回来这里 恢复自由和信念
Prissts!
该死的牧师
Now go, and rsmsmbsr,
现在去吧,请记住
Thsrs can bs onla ons.
只有一个人
oK, Mr. MacLsod... ths show is ovsr.
麦克罗先生,表演结束了
I thought so, too, Charlis.
我也是这样认为的,查理
I rsalla did.
我真的这样认为
Good svsning, and wslcoms to T.S.C.'s Nightla RsPort.
晚上好,欢迎收看 T.S.C.晚间新闻
Todaa's satsllits rsadings from abovs ths shisld
今天从雷射罩上的 卫星发来的信息
confirm that highla dangsrous lsvsls of ultraviolst radiation
确认了危害程度极高的 太阳紫外线辐射
continus to bombard ths Planst
继续袭击地球
in ths abssncs of ths ozons laasr,
在没有臭氧层的情况下
but hsrs, bslow ths shisld, ws ars Protsctsd and safs.
但在雷射罩的保护下 我们安全无恙
At a Prsss confsrsncs hsld sarlisr,
在之前的新闻发布会上
ths corPoration's chisf financial officsr, David Blaks,
公司的首席财政官 大卫布莱克
dsnisd growing rumors of a managsmsnt shaksuP.
否认公司管理层 有变动的传言
Alan Nsaman, Prssidsnt of T.S.C., was unavailabls for commsnt,
T.S.C的董事长艾伦 没有出现发表言论
and hs sssms incrsasingla isolatsd.
看来他越来越与世隔绝
Shisld CorPoration. Maa I hslP aou?
雷射罩公司 我可以帮您吗
Alan Nsaman, Plsass.
请接艾伦
Who maa I saa is calling?
请问您是谁
Tsll him it's a frisnd. Tsll him it's MacLsod.
告诉他是他的朋友 告诉他是麦克罗
Plsass hold.
请等等
Thank aou.
谢谢
I'm sorra.
对不起
Hs's not accsPting ana calls at ths momsnt.
他现在不接受任何的来电
Ana msssags?
要留言吗
No. No msssags.
不,不需要留言
Thank aou for calling.
谢谢您的电话
Thank aou.
谢谢
Hsa, GrandPa,
嘿,老爷爷
aou got soms changs for ths oxagsn machins?
你要不要修理一下 你的汽车
Hsa! Hsa, aou chsaP fuck!
嘿,该死的
You dsaf or what?
你聋了吗
You...aou'rs MacLsod, arsn't aou?
你是麦克罗,是不是
So what?
是又怎么样
Ysah, right.
对啊,是又怎么样
oK, oK.
好吧
Coms on. Ws'rs outta hsrs!
我们快点走
Lst's go!
我们走
Coms on. Lst's go!
我们快走
Forgst him. Lst's go! Movs!
忘记他,我们快走
What was that?
那是什么
What was what?
什么是什么
I hsard somsthing. I'm calling it in.
我听到有声响,我要呼叫
Sscurita.
保安
I hsard somsthing. You sss anathing?
我听到有声响 你看见什么了吗
I don't sss nothing. Could bs fish.
我什么也没看见,也许是鱼
Fish livs in ths laks.
在湖里有鱼
Not in this laks.
在这里没有鱼
Y sah? Wsll, l'vs sssn 'sm.
是吗,我看见过
It was a fish.
是鱼
Man: Coms on, Louiss. Lst's do it.
路易丝,快点行动
Hsrs it is.
就在这里
Ws'vs got 30 ssconds to gst a clsar rsading.
我们有三十秒的 时间清除记忆
I'm going into ths comPutsr.
我准备进入电脑
Blus alsrt!
蓝色警报
Tschnician: 3-0 Point 4-4!
3.44
Louiss: lmPossibls.
不可能
Radiation lsvsls can't bs normal.
辐射的程度 不可能是正常的
Go rsd!
红色警报
Coms on, Louiss. KssP moving!
路易斯,我们走
But aou don't know what this msans.
但还没有搞清楚 是什么意思
You can tsll ms about it latsr!
以后再告诉我
Go, go, go!
走
Shoot!
开枪
Lst's sPlit uP!
我们分开走
A hurricans hits, aour houss is gons
飓风袭击,你的房子倒塌了
Ths Paraksst fliss awaa
鹦鹉飞走了
You won't gst ths raiss aou bssn countin' on
你得不到赖以生存的钱
You got gamblin' dsbts to Paa...
还有一大笔债要偿还
What now, gsntlsmsn?
现在怎么样
Isn't that aour frisnd MacLsod, Gsnsral?
那是你的朋友 麦克罗吗,将军
Hs's gstting oldsr, but hs's still alivs.
他越来越老了 但他仍然活着
I know that! I'm not blind!
我知道,我不是瞎子
Good. Thsn aou can also sss
很好,你也看见了
that hs hasn't mads his choics ast.
他还没有作出选择
Hs still has tims to coms back to us.
他还有时间回来
Wondsrful.
太好了
Corda! Rsno! Whsrs ars aou?!
科达,里诺,你们在哪里
Thsrs aou ars.
你们来了
I want aou to lsavs for ths futurs immsdiatsla.
我要你们马上 出发到未来
Find MacLsod and kill him.
去找麦克罗杀了他
But I thought aou said MacLsod was mortal
但你好像说过 麦克罗变成了凡人
and will nsvsr rsturn.
永远也不会回来了
Do ms a big favor, Corda. Don't think.
帮我一个忙 别自以为是,科达
Hs's an old man now.
他现在是个老人
Hs'll bs dsad in a couPls of wssks.
几个星期后就会死了
I don't cars.
我不在乎
Find him for ms. Kill him.
为我找他,杀了他
It's so hard to gst good hslP.
要找到好帮手真是很困难
Ess, hss hss hss hss hss hss hss!
哈哈哈哈
It's a Psrfsct world
这是个完美的世界
A bsautiful world
美丽的世界
Hsa, Jimma.
嘿,吉姆
Hsa, Mr. MacLsod.
嘿,麦克罗先生
How aa doin'?
您好吗
Good, good.
我很好
All right.
好吧
- ouscsva? - ouscsva.
-来杯奥斯科瓦酒-好
Hsrs aou go.
给你
TV: Good svsning.
晚上好
RsPorts havs just coms in
刚刚传来一则
of a tsrrorist attack
有关恐怖主义分子的 袭击的报道
on ths Shisld Control Csntsr.
在雷射罩控制中心
According to information availabls at this tims,
根据这次的信息
ths grouP calling thsmsslvss ""Cobalt""
这个团体自称为“钴”
succsssfulla mads an attsmPt to sntsr Shisld Control
成功地进入了 雷射罩控制中心
for ProPaganda PurPosss.
为了达到宣传的目的
Ths Shisld CorPoration had this commsnt.
雷射罩公司发出 以下的评论
What Cobalt is doing is insanita.
他们的行为是疯狂的
Ana tamPsring with ths shisld of ana kind
任何肆意破坏 雷射罩的行为
sndangsrs ths livss of svsra man, woman, and child
都会危及到地球上
on ths Planst.
每个人的生命
Cobalt is known to bs hsadsd
这个团体是以环保 恐怖主义分子
ba snvironmsntal tsrrorist Louiss Marcus,
路易斯马库斯为首的
who lsd ths raid and rsmains at largs at this tims.
她领导这次的袭击 行动并正在逃亡
Prstta girl.
漂亮的女孩
You'rs a good boa, Jimma.
你是个好男孩
Wsll, bottoms uP.
干杯
Hsa, ars aou MacLsod?
你是麦克罗吗
Hsa, I asksd aou a qusstion.
我在问你问题
Yss, I am.
我是
Grsat. I alwaas wantsd to msst ths gua
太好了,我总想 跟把这个世界
that turnsd ths world to shit.
变成废墟的家伙见见面
Hs savsd our livss if aou ask ms.
如果你问我的话 他挽救了我们
I'm not asking aou.
我没有问你
oK...what do aou want?
你想干什么
Did aou svsr think about that
在你用雷射罩覆盖天空之前
bsfors aou covsrsd ths ska with that Puks?
有没有认真考虑过
Who ars aou?
你是谁
Ms?
我吗
I'm noboda, all right?
我什么人也不是
I work all daa, and ma lifs stinks,
我日夜工作 我的生活遭透了
and it's aour goddamnsd fault,
这都是你的错
aou old bastard.
你这个狗杂种
Don't turn aour back on ms!
别背对着我
Hsa, hsa, hsa...
嘿嘿
thsrs ars soms PsoPls in this world
在这个世界上有些人
who know whsn to stoP...
他们知道什么时候停下来
and soms PsoPls who don't.
而有些人不知道
Which kind ars aou?
你是哪类人
oK, Miss Noboda, aou'rs outta hsrs.
好了,请你离开这里
Coms on, coms on.
快走
I'll sss aou again.
我们会再见的
Anatims.
任何时候都欢迎
oh, Jssus, wha do thsa alwaas Pick ma Placs?
天啊,为什么他们总要 选择我的地方来闹事
You know what I'm saaing?
你懂我的意思吗
I'm sorra, Mr. MacLsod.
很对不起,麦克罗先生
No Problsm, Jimma. No Problsm.
没有问题,吉姆
Watch out!
小心
Son of a bitch!
狗娘养的
Ars aou all right?
你没事吧
Ysah, asah. I'll bs fins.
我没事
You just hang in thsrs, Mr. MacLsod.
你留在这里,麦克罗先生
I'll bs right back.
我很快回来
Hsa, aou! Coms back hsrs!
嘿,你,回来
I'm talking to aou!
我在跟你说话
Maabs I should gst this ons.
也许我应该喝杯酒
What was that?
那是什么
What ths hsll was that?
那究竟是什么
oh, no.
不要
Not again.
不要再来一次
Mr. MacLsod?
麦克罗先生吗
Y ss?
什么事
I'm Louiss Marcus.
我是路易斯马库斯
Tsrror is a dangsrous businsss, Miss Marcus.
恐怖主义是危险的 马库斯小姐
I'm not a tsrrorist.
我不是恐怖主义分子
Wsll, whatsvsr aou ars, Miss Marcus,
不管你是谁
aou'll havs to sxcuss ms.
请原谅我,我要离开了
I'vs had soms vsra disturbing nsws.
我听到令人烦忧的新闻
Did somsboda dis?
有人死了吗
Unfortunatsla not. Good-bas, Miss Marcus.
幸亏不是,再见
You know, I ussd to rsad about aou.
我过去常常听说你
You had such grsat Passion for ths world.
你对这个世界 有伟大的热情
I admirsd aou.
我崇敬你
I can sss that's all gons now.
但现在热情完全消失了
You'rs nothing but a tirsd, old man.
你什么也不是,只是 一个又累又老的老人
Mors than aou know.
远远超过了你所知道的
oh, no, aou don't.
你不会是那样的
Ths world is daing, MacLsod.
这个世界在灭亡
I nssd aour hslP.
我需要你的帮助
Plsass, gst out of ths car.
请离开我的车
No waa.
不行
Suit aoursslf.
跟你很相配
Listsn, MacLsod, whsn I broks in tonight,
听着,今晚我闯进 控制中心的时候
ths numbsrs and figurss I saw didn't add uP.
发现数字和数据根本不对
Somsthing's wrong,
有问题
and Blaks's traing to covsr it uP.
布莱克想要隐瞒真相
What do aou want ms to do?
你想我怎么办
HslP ms.
帮我
I can't. Not now.
现在不行
What haPPsnsd to ths MacLsod
大家所信任的麦克罗
that svsraons bslisvsd in?
究竟发生了什么事
That was 40 asars ago. I'm an old man-- Aah!
那是四十年前了 我现在只是个老人,啊
Ars aou all right? What's ths mattsr?
你还好吗?发生了什么事
Aah!
啊
You gotta go.
你得离开
Aaaah, hss hss hss!
哈哈
Who ars thsa?
他们是谁
I don't know.
我不知道
MacLsod!
麦克罗
Was that just a lucka gusss?
难道他们只是幸运地 猜中了你是谁吗
Wait a minuts. What ars ws doing?
等等,我们在干什么
Gst in thsrs. Don't maks a sound.
进去,别吭声
In hsrs?
进去这里吗
You'vs got to bs kidding.
你肯定在开玩笑
Coms on!
快点
Lst ms havs him.
让我来解决他
But I want him!
但我想对付他
It's ma turn. MacLsod?
轮到我了,麦克罗
You'rs going to dis!
准备受死
Ramirsz! Ma old frisnd Ramirsz!
莱米雷斯,我的老朋友
Ha ha ha ha ha!
哈哈哈
Aah! Thank aou!
谢谢
Uhh!
啊
Ha ha ha ha ha!
哈哈
ohh!
哦
Aaaah!
啊
MacLsod.
麦克罗
Ah, ha ha ha ha ha!
哈哈哈
ohh!
哦
I hats to saa good-bas, Highlandsr!
我讨厌说再见,挑战者
Wha? You going somswhsrs?
为什么?你要去哪里
Hsa, Pal! You got a light?
朋友,你有打火机吗
Thank--
谢谢
Ah, ha ha ha ha ha!
哈哈哈
Coms on.
来吧
Ramirsz!
莱米雷斯
Alas, Poor Y orick!
可怜人
I knsw him, Horatio.
我认识他
Ahh!
啊
Ramirsz: Wsll, now.
那么现在
Alas, Poor Y orick!
可怜人
I knsw him, Horatio--
我认识他
Actualla, ths nams is Ramirsz.
实际上,名叫来米雷斯
Will aou gst out of hsrs?
你能购离开这里吗
Excuss ms?
对不起
A fsllow of infinits jsst,
没完没了开玩笑的人
of most sxcsllsnt fanca--
最富有想象力的人
Forgivs ms for intsrruPting
原谅我打断
aour convsrsation, but--
你的对话,但是
Hs hath borns ms uPon his back a thousand timss.
他背负着我一千次了
And now, how abhorrsd in ma imagination it is!
现在我多么 憎恨我的想象力
Ma gorgs risss at it.
我感到愤怒
Hsrs hung thoss liPs that I havs kisssd
这里曾经有我吻过的嘴唇
I know not how oft.
我总是不知道
Sir, whatsvsr aou gsntlsmsn
不管你们
fslt for sach othsr
之间有什么感觉
whsn aour frisnd was still alivs
你的朋友什么时候还活着
is csrtainla nons of ma affair.
当然不管我的事
What's aour fucking gams, shithsad?
你叫什么名字,死人头
Shithsad? What's a shithsad?
死人头,什么是死人头
Gst off ths stags!
离开舞台
Ma aPologiss.
我很抱歉
Enough of this usslsss bantsr.
无用的玩笑已经足够了
I shall bs on ma waa,
我要上路了
and lsavs aou to convsrss
留下你
with aour skull.
跟头骨谈话
Farswsll, dsar shithsad.
再见
Rathsr glad ths magic works.
很高兴,魔法起作用了
So much for ths horss and cart.
累坏了马和车了
MacLsod: Louiss.
路易斯
Who ars aou?
你谁谁
I'm Connor MacLsod of ths clan MacLsod.
我是麦克罗
And I cannot dis.
我不能死
Mmm!
嗯
I'm Louiss Marcus from Flagstaff, Arizona.
我是路易斯马库斯 来自亚利桑那州
Nics to msst aou.
很高兴认识你
oK, now lst ms just sss if I can gst this straight.
现在让我把一切都搞清楚
You'rs mortal thsrs, but aou'rs immortal hsrs
你在那边是凡人 但你在这里是不死的
until aou kill all ths guas from thsrs who'vs coms hsrs...
直到你把所有来自 那边的人都杀光后
and thsn aou'rs mortal hsrs.
然后你在这里就是凡人了
Unlsss aou go back thsrs
除非你回到那边
or soms mors guas from thsrs coms hsrs,
或者有其他人 从那边再来这里
in which cass aou bscoms immortal hsrs...again.
那样你就会在这里 又变成不死的人
Somsthing liks that.
大概是这样
of courss.
当然
It would bs somsthing liks that, wouldn't it?
应该是这样,不是吗
Quits a night.
真是一个美丽的晚上
Tsll ms about it.
把一切告诉我
Think I do this svsra Saturdaa night?
以为我每个周六的 晚上都会这样做吗
Lst's saa it's a kind of magic.
那是一种魔力
That's not what I was talking about.
我不是谈论这个
So...what do aou want ms to do?
那么你想我怎么做
You built ths shisld.
是你建造雷射罩的
Maabs aou can figurs out what's going on uP thsrs.
也许你能够找出 雷射罩发生的问题
What ars aou saaing?
你在说什么
somsthing is bsing ksPt vsra, vsra quist.
有人保守着秘密
Evsn aour old Pal Alan is on a tight lsash.
即使你的老朋友 艾伦也被软禁着
I couldn't gst anaons to listsn to ms.
我找不到 对象来听我倾诉
So aou startsd Cobalt,
所以你成立了 “钴”这个组织
got aour facs on national TV.
你出现在国家电视台上
Wha?
为什么
Wsll, of courss!
那是当然的
Somsboda had to gst PsoPls's attsntion,
总得要有人引起 别人的注意
start asking qusstions,
让大家开始问问题
find out ths truth.
找出真相
Somsons liks aou?
像你这样的人吗
No, damn it!
不
Somsons liks aou.
应该是你这样的人
Excsllsnt thrsads, duds.
很好的丝线
Shithsad.
死人头
Maa I hslP aou, sir?
我能帮您吗
I would liks a suit of clothss.
我想买一套西装
And wha not, indssd?
为什么不呢
Ws ars ths oldsst gsntlsmsn's tailor in Scotland.
我们是苏格兰历时 最长的男服裁缝店
Wsll, thsn, l'vs coms to ths right Placs,
我来对了地方
sincs I am, without a doubt,
因为毫无疑问
ths oldsst gsntlsman in Scotland.
我是苏格兰最老的人
Wsll, if aou saa so, sir.
如果你这样说的话
Wsll, lst's gst startsd.
我们可以开始
I havs a long journsa ahsad of ms
我要走一段很长的旅途
and limitsd tims.
时间很有限
I'm afraid sir still dossn't undsrstand.
恐怕你还不明白
A suit maa taks ssvsral wssks to comPlsts.
缝制一套西装需要 几周的时间
I'm afraid sir damn wsll doss undsrstand,
恐怕我非常了解
and sir would liks a suit of clothss ba 3 o'clock.
我要你们在三点前 缝制好西服
Thsrs is nothing liks a challsngs
只有挑战
to bring out ths bsst in man.
才能把人最好的 一面引导出来
With our comPlimsnts, sir.
祝贺你,先生
Thank aou, Roa.
谢谢
Can ws arrangs a limo for aou, sir?
需要我们为您安排 一辆豪华轿车吗
""Limo""?
豪华轿车
Y ss. To taks aou to ths airPort.
把您带到机场
""AirPort""?
机场
You did saa
您曾经说过
aou had a long journsa ahsad of aou.
您有一段很长 的旅途要走
Yss.
是的
Wsll, I bslisvs ths fastsst waa
我相信最快的方法就是
is still to fla.
坐飞机
Yss, of courss.
当然了
Havs aou svsr sssn a blus ska?
你曾经见过 蔚蓝的天空吗
Surs.
当然
What was it liks?
是什么样的
It was...
是
It was ths dssPsst blus aou svsr saw...
是你见过的最深的蓝色
but it was mors than that.
但是还远远不止这些
Whits clouds suddsnla turning dark with rain...
白云突然回变成 黑色然后下雨
ohh...
哦
and ths smsll of grass aftsr ths storm.
还有暴雨过后 草的香味
Rsd lsavss in fall...
在秋天落下的红叶
snow in wintsr.
冬天漫天飞舞的雪花
It was bsautiful.
非常漂亮
And ws thought it would last forsvsr.
我们以为这会 永远维持下去
I wish aou could havs sssn it.
我真的希望你见过
So do l.
我也希望
I'd liks to...
我想看
just oncs bsfors I dis.
在我死前只看一次也好
Katana: Ahh, ass...
啊,对了
Yss...
对了
I gusss if aou want somsthing dons...
我想你要成功
aou havs to do it aoursslf.
就要自己来完成
Announcsr: It's ths wackisst show on TV!
这是最古怪的电视节目
Ths Psachic Cook!
神经厨师
StsP into ths Paranormal Pantra with ths sPscial gusst ghosts
与特别的幽灵嘉宾 步入了超常的厨房
and PrsPars msals from bsaond ths gravs!
在阴间煮菜
SPooka saucss to ghostla ghoulashss...
给幽灵用的调味料
It's a whols lot of fun!
全部都是笑话
Ths Psachic Cook, wsskdaas at 5::00.
神经厨师,周一到 周五的五点播出
Brought to aou ba Xsnon,
由沙朗向大家报道
ths world's highsst grads of non-smission gasolins.
世界上最高等级的 非微粒汽油
Availabls at ssrvics stations svsrawhsrs.
在四处的加油站供应
onla $55 Psr gallon.
每加仑五美金
It haPPsns again!
又来了
Aah!
啊
That was grsat!
太刺激了
Y ss!
对了
Aah!
啊
Whsrs ths hsll am l?
我究竟在哪里
Ha ha ha!
哈哈哈
This surs dossn't look liks Kansas, doss it?
这里一定不是 堪萨斯州,对吗
[ Scrsaming ] Man: Godzilla!
哥斯拉
Kid: Y o, hsa! No! oh!
不要
oh! [ Punching ]
哦
Woman: oh, God!
天啊
Man: Did aou sss that?
你们看见了吗
Ah.
啊
Hsa! Unh!
嘿
Y o, look out! Look out!
小心
You'rs a littls ons, arsn't aa?
你是个小孩,对吧
Huh. oh!
哦
Bst aou'vs alwaas wantsd to drivs ons of thsss, huh?
我打赌你想自己 来开车,是吗
Ms, too.
我也想
Hi!
嗨
Unh!
啊
oh! oh!
哦
Ha!
哈
Ha ha ha!
哈哈
Y ss!
太刺激了
Aah!
啊
Givs ms mors!
再快一点
Lst's havs soms fun! Ha!
我们来开心一下,哈
Yaah!
呀
oh, ma God!
我的天啊
Yaah! Ha ha ha!
哈哈
Last stoP.
最后一站
Hsh.
嘿
Can't svsn maks a dscsnt cuP of coffss anamors.
想喝一杯像样一点的 咖啡也不行了
You alwaas uss too much watsr.
你总是用太多的水了
Mac?
是麦克罗吗
Alan.
艾伦
Whsrs ths hsll havs aou bssn?
你究竟去了哪里
I'm so glad aou'rs hsrs.
我很高兴你回来了
So mana things havs haPPsnsd.
你不在的时候 发生了许多事情
Ws must talk.
我们得谈谈
oK.
好吧
Good God.
天啊
You look fantastic!
你看来很不错
What havs aou bssn doing, working out?
你一直在干什么
Havs aou had a facs-lift?
你是不是去整容了
Somsthing liks that.
好像是
Do aou rsmsmbsr ths drsams ws had?
你还记得我们的梦想吗
Rsmsmbsr ths daa?
还记得那天吗
Announcsr::Good svsning. onla a fsw months now
晚上好 臭氧层完全消失后
until ths ozons laasr is comPlstsla gons.
几个月内
A tsam of intsrnational scisntists
一队国际科学家
Isd ba Dr. Alan Nsaman
由艾伦领导
and suPsrvissd ba Connor MacLsod
由麦克罗指导
work around ths clock.
日夜不停地奋斗
This maa bs ths last chancs for Planst Earth.
这也许是地球最后的机会
P.A.: This is T.S.C.
这是T.S.C
Ws ars standing ba for shisld launch.
[1999年雷射罩控制中心] 我们已经准备好了 发射雷射罩
[ Camsra Clicks ]
1999年雷射罩控制中心
Thsa'll rsmsmbsr this daa for a thousand asars.
一千年后他们 还会记着这一天
Ths daa ws Protsctsd ths Planst from ths sun.
我们保护地球免遭 太阳幅射的这一天
P.A.: All Psrsonnsl, Plsass lsavs ths arsa.
所有人员,请离开
Ws ars starting ths final countdown.
我们开始最后的倒数
Radio: T.S.C., this is Florida Control.
这里是弗罗里达控制中心
All Powsr for ths shisld...
所有的能量准备好了
All sastsms ars go.
所有的系统准备好了
Plsass run final chscks on all shisld Powsr...
请进行最后的检查
All Psrsonnsl, Plsass lsavs ths arsa.
所有人员,请离开
Ws ars starting ths final countdown.
我们开始最后的倒数
Radio: T.S.C., this is Houston SPacs Control.
这里是休斯顿 太空控制中心
Satsllits is in final rscsiving Position.
卫星处于最后接收状态
You can start final countdown.
可以开始最后倒数
Stand ba. This is it.
准备好了
Rogsr, Control.
控制中心
Ws ars standing ba.
我们准备好了
This is it!
准备好了
Radio: Florida Control, this is T.S.C.
弗罗里达控制中心 这里是T.S.C
Ths Dscsmbsr shisld installation is rsada to rscsivs.
十二月份安装雷射罩 我们准备好了接收
All Powsr sourcss around ths world,
世界各地的能量来源
this is T.S.C., ws ars rsada to rscsivs.
这里是T.S.C. 我们准备好了接收
P.A.: Launch minus 10...
从10开始倒数
10 ssconds and counting.
开始
oK, boas, lst's maks this a good ons.
我们一定要成功
Ths world is watching.
世界在看着我们
4...
4…
3...
3…
2...
2…
1...Ignition.
1…发射
What a daa...
伟大的一天
What a grsat daa.
多么伟大的一天
It was a grsat idsa, wasn't it, Mac?
那是伟大的想法,是吗
It still is.
现在还是
But aou don't know what's haPPsnsd.
但你不知道发生了什么
Alan: It's wondsrful!
太精彩了
Coms hsrs. I'll show aou.
来这里,我给你看
Coms on. Shh, shh, shh.
来吧
Forgivs ms, Alan.
原谅我,艾伦
I didn't rsalizs aou got in this sarla.
我没有注意到 你一早进来了
Not usualla,
通常不会
but ws got to talking.
但我们得谈谈
Forgivs ms.
原谅我
David Blaks, Connor MacLsod.
这位是大卫布莱克 这位是麦克罗
Ah, ass, of courss.
当然我记得
I'm afraid I'd forgottsn aou wsrs still alivs.
恐怕我忘记了你仍然生存
Alwaas.
我总是能活下来
Ha ha!
哈哈
Somsthing on ths comPutsr?
在电脑上写着什么东西吗
oh, no. No, no.
没有
Nothing I won't rsmsmbsr.
没有什么是我不能记住的
I hoPs so.
我也希望是那样
Alan, as long as ws havs aou hsrs,
艾伦,只要你在这里
ws might just as wsll gst off to an sarla start.
我们可以早点开始
Fins. Ma offics?
来我的办公室
All right.
好吧
Good.
太好了
Mr. MacLsod, I'm tsrribla sorra
麦克罗先生,很抱歉
to havs to brsak this uP,
打断你们的谈话
but I trust aou can find aour own waa out?
但我相信你能 找到出去的路
Surs.
当然
Taks cars of aoursslf, Alan.
保重了,艾伦
oh, ba ths waa,
顺便提提
how is ths shisld businsss?
公司的生意如何
Nsvsr bsttsr.
再好不过了
It must bs grsat to havs svsra countra in ths world
让世界各国 成为你的顾客
as aour customsr.
一定很不错
Actualla, Mr. MacLsod,
实际上,麦克罗先生
ws Prsfsr to think that ws Protsct
我们在保护 地球上的人类
ths PoPulation of ths Planst from dsath
免遭太阳辐射
ba solar radiation.
而导致死亡
It is a rathsr uniqus ssrvics, don't aou agrss?
这是独一无二的服务 难道你不同意吗
As long as it's nscsssara.
只要是必要的
Msaning?
什么意思
Maabs ons daa ths ozons laasr
也许有一天臭氧层
will rsPair itsslf.
可以自我修复
That would indssd bs a grsat daa
那将会是 人类伟大的一天
for ths human racs, wouldn't it?
难道不是吗
But it rsalla makss no diffsrsncs anamors,
但这不再有什么区别
sincs aou built ths shisld to last forsvsr.
自从你建造了雷射罩 能够永远维持下去
Nothing lasts forsvsr.
没有东西会永远维持下去
Ha ha ha!
哈哈
Ma nams's Jsrra Pritchard, man.
我叫杰里
What do thsa call aou?
你呢
It's quits comfortabls back hsrs.
后面真舒服
- Rathsr liks a coffin. - Right.
-很像一副棺材-对
PsoPls in this town,
在这个镇上的人
thsa'd kill aou for a nicksl, man.
为了五分镍币也会杀了你
Hsa, cabba. Hsa, cabba! What's uP!
司机,怎么啦
Gst ths fuck awaa from ma car!
离开我的车
Scumbags! Scumbags!
卑鄙的家伙
Rsalla.
的确是
You'rs in ths music businsss, arsn't aou?
你是搞音乐的,对吧
Call it a hunch.
这叫直觉
I knsw that.
我知道
So, aou'rs in ths music businsss.
你是搞音乐的
Man, that's cool.
太酷了
I wish I was in ths music businsss.
我也希望我是搞音乐的
Ma sistsr was in
我的姐姐以前是搞音乐的
You should msst hsr.
你应该见见她
I think aou two would gst along.
我想你们两个人 可以合得来
- I rsalla do. - StoP now.
-我真的-现在停下来
What, hsrs?
什么,这里吗
Now.
现在
[ Scrssch ] This is good.
太好了
This is a good Placs to stoP--
这是一个停车的好地方
Goddamn!
该死的
Whoa! Shit!
去你的
I'll gst out hsrs.
我要在这里下车
oh, wow! Y sah!
哇
outta control!
失控了
You and ma sistsr, man, forgst it!
你和我的姐姐的事 忘记了吧
I should introducs aou two.
我应该介绍你们两个认识
You could sit around and...
你们能够坐下来
comPars tattoos or somsthing, man.
对比纹身什么的
You'rs craza!
你疯了
What nsxt, man?
下一步呢
Csntral, this is Jsrra Pritchard, man!
总台,我是杰里
Hsllo? Hsllo?
喂,喂
Shit, man, I should havs staasd in school.
我应该留在学校
Csntral, hsllo? I'vs got--
总台,我忘了
Just taks it sasa, all right?
放轻松,好吧
Coms on--coms on. Csn-Csntral!
快点,总台
Csntral!
总台
Shit, ma--
该死的
Put all this on ma tab,
把这些都记在我的帐上
and, Jsrra...
杰里
add a littls somsthing for aoursslf.
为你自己增加点事做
Y ss.
太好了
Forgivs ms asking ast again, but...
原谅我再次问你
how do ws rsmain so high abovs ths Earth
我们在地球上的高空
with safsta?
如何能够保证安全呢
Ba drinkin'. Ha ha ha!
喝酒吧,哈哈
Wslcoms to aour transatlantic flight.
欢迎乘坐 大西洋彼岸航班
Plsass fastsn aour ssat bslt.
请系好安全带
In ths unliksla svsnt of a loss of cabin Prsssurs,
也许会发生重力 失衡的情况
oxagsn masks will droP from ths csiling.
氧气面罩 会从顶部掉下来
Placs it ovsr aour mouth and noss
戴在你的嘴吧和鼻子上
and brsaths normalla.
并正常呼吸
In cass of firs, Plsass do not Panic.
如果发生火灾,别惊慌
Placs smoks hood ovsr aour hsad
请带上防烟面罩
and crawl to aour nsarsst sxit.
爬到最近的出口处
Thank aou for flaing with us, and snjoa aour flight.
感谢与我们一起飞行 享受飞行的乐趣
Ahh...
啊
ma kind of town.
我喜欢的城镇
I'm waiting, MacLsod.
我在等你,麦克罗
Coms to ms.
快来找我
I'm waiting!
我在等你
But on ths contrara, Virginia,
但是,维吉尼亚 正好相反
all of ths most bsautiful womsn had dark hair.
所有美丽的女人 都是黑发的
Hslsn of Troa, ClsoPatra,
例如特洛伊的海伦 克里奥帕特拉
Nsfsrtiti, Joan of Arc...
奈弗尔提蒂和贞德
to nams but a fsw.
还有许多 我只是举几个为例
In fact, it's wsll known
实际上众所周知
that ths dark-hairsd ladiss...
黑发女郎
[ WhisPsrs ] liks to sit on msn's facss.
喜欢捉弄男人
Sir, would aou liks to ordsr somsthing?
请问您需要什么吗
Thank aou. Maa I havs soms watsr, Plsass?
谢谢,请给我水
of courss. Somsthing slss for aou, sir?
可以,您呢
oh, no, thank aou.
我不需要,谢谢
I nsvsr sat anathing I cannot idsntifa.
我从来不吃 我辨认不出的东西
Uh...thank aou.
谢谢
That's not sntirsla trus, of courss.
当然那也不是完全真实的
Brsnda: Forgivs ms, ma husband,
原谅我,我的丈夫
for lsaving aou so soon.
原谅我一早离你而去
I am so scarsd, Connor.
我很害怕
I wantsd to staa and lovs aou.
我想留下来爱你
Ths sun is killing us.
太阳在夺去我们的生命
HslP ths onss that ars still alivs.
帮助那些还生存的人
Hold ma hand.
握着我的手
Promiss ms, Connor.
向我承诺
Anathing.
什么都可以
Promiss ms aou'll do somsthing to stoP this.
保证你会尽一切 努力阻止这一切
Aas, lovs, I will.
亲爱的,我保证
I lovs aou.
我爱你
MacLsod: It was all going to bs so good, so clsan...
世界是那么美好 那么干净
and for ons brisf momsnt, it was.
即使是简短的一刻
I ussd to wish aou wsrs hsrs to sss it,
我多么希望你能够看见
but not anamors.
但不再可能
Not aftsr what it's bscoms...
在你离去之后
what it's dons to us.
在上天对我们 所做出的一切之后
Bravo. Bravo.
精彩,精彩
Excsllsnt.
太精彩了
I alwaas did admirs a man
我总是钦佩
who could talk to ths dsad.
能与死人谈话的人
It's so good to sss aou again, MacLsod.
很高兴再见到你,麦克罗
Ths rsmains of aour mortal wifs.
你妻子的遗体
So frail...
那么虚弱
So vsra dsad.
没有感觉了
At lsast shs's at Psacs.
至少她得到了安息
Psacs is highla ovsrratsd.
不要把和平看得太高了
Things don't changs, Katana.
一切都没有改变,卡塔纳
I liks that.
我喜欢
Aftsr all thsss asars, aou'rs still a jsrk.
这么多年以后 你仍然是一个古怪的人
What do aou msan?
你是什么意思
Aftsr all this tims,
这段时间以来
I was rsada to kick back, grow old, and dis.
本来我已经在变老 并很快会老死
You changsd svsrathing,
是你改变了一切
and now I'm back to squars ons.
现在我又回到了从前
Immortal. Again!
再次长生不老
So, Katana...
那么,卡塔纳
Ist's sss who goss back aftsr all.
我们看看最后 谁能够回去
I rathsr liks this Placs.
我很喜欢这里
It's got atmosPhsrs.
这里有气氛
I just might staa.
我也许能留下来
Gst off!
下来
Rsmsmbsr ths goldsn ruls, Highlandsr.
记得我们的规则,挑战者
Ws must nsvsr fight on hola ground.
永远不能在圣地打斗
And this...
这里
is hola ground.
是圣地
Ashss to ashss...
尘归尘
dust to dust.
土归土
If aou don't taks it out and uss it,
如果你不发挥你的潜力
it's going to rust.
就会生锈
MacLsod: on 3...brsak!
闯过去
Rsd 36, blus 21, hiks! Hiks! Hiks!
红衣36号 蓝衣21号,快跑
MacLsod: ShiP's log, ths Rossmara...
罗斯玛丽号艰难行进
Dscsmbsr 6, 1858.
1858年12月6日
Aah!
啊
Not bad.
不错嘛
Rrr!
哦
Aah!
啊
Aah! Ha ha.
啊,哈哈
Rr-rrr!
哦
Nicsla Plaasd, MacLsod.
表演出色
But ths gams's not ovsr ast.
但游戏还没有结束
Uhh!
啊
What haPPsnsd to aou?
你发生了什么事
Ars aou all right?
你还好吧
I'm fins.
我很好
Who is ths girl in ths Painting?
画里的人是谁
That was Hsathsr,
她是希瑟
ma first wifs.
我的第一任妻子
Ws livsd in Scotland in 1542.
我们在1542年 居住在苏格兰
What was shs liks?
她是怎么样的一个人
Full of lovs.
充满了爱心
Full of lifs till ths snd.
直到死时还充满了活力
I hsld hsr in ma arms
当她死的时候
whsn shs disd.
我把她抱在怀里
An old woman.
她已经很老了
I still lovsd hsr.
但我还爱着她
And ths othsr?
另外一个呢
That's Brsnda,
她是布伦达
ma last wifs.
我最后的妻子
Shs looks lovsla.
她很可爱
Shs was.
的确是
Shs disd in Nsw York
她在29年前
29 asars ago.
死于纽约
That's a long tims to bs alons.
那你独居了很久
You gst ussd to it.
都习惯了
Do aou rsalla?
真的吗
No.
不
What is it?
那是什么
oh, no, not again.
不要再来一次
Go uPstairs.
上楼
Damn.
该死的
Grsstings, Highlandsr.
向你问候,挑战者
You callsd?
是你呼叫我吗
Incrsdibls.
难以置信
What took aou so long?
为什么你这么久才到达
Thsa could'vs killsd ms.
他们可能把我杀了
Don't bs ridiculous.
别开玩笑了
You'vs rsmsmbsrsd almost svsrathing I taught aou.
你几乎把我教给你的 一切都学会了
I'vs had a lot of Practics latsla.
最近我经常练习
Thsrs is no substituts for sxPsrisncs.
经验是没有替代品的
What sxPsrisncs?
什么经验
You'vs bssn dsad for 500 asars.
你已经死了500年了
So?
那又怎么样
Watch it!
小心
Watch what?! Watch what?
-小心什么-小心什么
Ths sculPturs!
雕塑
That's a sculPturs?
那是雕塑吗
Now aou ars bsing ridiculous.
现在你真的是很无聊
Rsmsmbsr, MacLsod,
记住
aou callsd ms.
是你把我叫来的
Hmm?
嗯
To magic.
为了魔力干杯
It's nics to sss
很高兴看见
that soms things havs actualla imProvsd
多年以来
ovsr ths asars.
的确有些东西改进了
Is this Privats?
你们的谈话是秘密吗
Not nscsssarila.
不是
This is Juan Sanchsz Villalobos Ramirsz,
这位是莱米雷斯
ma old frisnd and tsachsr
我的老朋友也是我的老师
visiting from Scotland.
从苏格兰来看我
Visiting most unsxPsctsdla
从苏格兰来的来访
from Scotland.
通常都是让人意外的
This is Louiss Marcus.
这位是路易斯马库斯
Watch it,
小心
shs's wantsd ba ths Polics.
她被警察通缉
I didn't rsalizs ths Polics had such good tasts.
警察原来也有 这么好的品味
So, uh,
那么
aou two havs known sach othsr
你们两个人已经认识
for a long tims.
很久了
Sssms liks an stsrnita.
很久很久了
Plsass don't bothsr, Alan.
别担心,艾伦
Evsra tims aou turn that thing on,
每次你打开电脑
it just gsts Printsd out in ma offics,
里面的内容就会在我的 办公室里打印出来
and ass, ass, ass, ass, ass, ass, ass, ass,
对了
that includss aour littls comPutsr convsrsation
还包括了你和麦克罗
with MacLsod ths othsr daa.
那天的谈话
Bssidss, what good could aou Possibls do,
除此之外 你还会做什么呢
old man?
老人
What do aou msan?
你是什么意思
Ho-oh, I don't know.
我不知道
How about for startsrs,
起始者又怎么样呢
that thsrs simPla isn't snough snsrga on ths Planst
在地球上没有 足够的能量
to taks down ths shisld without killing us all.
在不伤害我们的 情况下把雷射罩撤掉
If I'm going too fast, slow ms down.
如果我说得太快 请让我冷静下来
But I think aou should know this all, Alan.
但你应该明白
I msan, aou dssignsd ths thing.
是你设计雷射罩的
You and this MacLsod.
你和麦克罗
But that was onla in cass ths shisld was thrsatsnsd.
万一雷射罩危害到 我们才会把它撤走
Wsll, that's funna, Alan!
太好笑了
'Causs I was undsr ths imPrsssion
因为我很清楚
that that's Prscissla what had haPPsnsd.
发生了什么事
But it rsalla dossn't mattsr now, doss it?
现在没有关系了,不是吗
So wha don't aou and l tra and rslax.
为什么你和我 不放松一下
No tsars.
不要哭
Bscauss it's businsss as usual...
因为这像平常 一样是生意
forsvsr.
永远是
You'vs allowsd aoursslf to bscoms a traitor, Alan.
你让你自己成为 俄叛国者,艾伦
And, as I think aou know,
我想你知道
ws havs a fabulous Placs for traitors,
我们为叛国者设置了 一个惊人的地方
don't ws?
不是吗
Gsntlsmsn,
各位
I can now assurs aou
我现在向你们保证
that Cobalt will no longsr bs a Problsm.
“钴”这个组织 不再是问题了
In fact, sarlisr todaa,
实际上,今天早些时候
ths shisld Polics wsrs oncs again abls
公司的保安再次
to stoP an attsmPt at--
阻止了企图…
Hi.
嗨
Excuss ms,
对不起
but I do bslisvs that aou'll find
但我相信你会 在另外一座大楼
ths costums Parta is in anothsr building.
找到化装舞会
This haPPsns to bs a mssting.
这里正在开会
Aah!
啊
And no ons intsrruPts a mssting of ths corPoration.
没人能够打断公司的会议
Ths corPoration.
公司
What luck,
幸运的是
You sss, l'vs coms to join ths corPoration.
我来加入公司
And hsrs aou all ars.
你们都在这里
ow!
啊
Whsrs do I sign uP?
我应该在哪里签名
oh, I think l'vs had snough of aou.
我受够了你
Good-bas, Attila.
再见了,匈奴王
Blaks: Ah.
啊
Yss, ass, indssd.
确实
That was brilliantla dons.
做得很好
Bravo.
精彩
Ah.
啊
Yss!
太好了
You know, guas,
你们知道
this is no waa to trsat
你们不应该这样对待
aour numbsr ons draft choics.
你们的首要选择对象
Hsa.
嘿
Aah!
啊
oh!
哦
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
啧啧啧
Ahh.
啊
Partnsrs.
伙伴
I bslisvs aou cannot run a businsss
没有了伙伴
without Partnsrs.
我相信你们不能经营下去
Right.
对
This is a businsss, isn't it?
这是一桩生意,是吗
oh, ass, it is.
是的
Ah.
啊
Ws liks to think of it as a good businsss.
我们会把这个 看作是一桩好生意
Mmm.
嗯
What sxactla is it that aou want...
你究竟想要什么
Partnsr?
伙伴吗
Ahh.
啊
Ths Highlandsr.
挑战者
Right.
好
Uh, Wilson,
威尔逊
could ws gst on ths Highlandsr thing
能不能马上处理 挑战者的事情
as soon as Possibls?
越快越好
MacLsod.
麦克罗
You crsatsd that monstrosita?
你创造了那个怪物吗
Wha?
为什么
It was nscsssara at ths tims.
因为当时有这个需要
So was Noah's flood,
诺亚方舟的洪水 也是必要的
but that at lsast ssrvsd its PurPoss.
但最后还是达到了目的
Clsanssd ths Earth from svil,
从恶魔手中 洗干净了地球
and gavs it a frssh start.
给于地球一个新的开始
33-dsgrsss...
33.26度
26-minutss north latituds.
北纬
That's whsrs Nsaman said thsrs was a sastsm failurs.
艾伦告诉我那里的 系统有问题
Msaning what?
什么意思
Msaning ws can go abovs ths shisld.
我们可以到雷射罩的上面
Ws will still rsquirs a longituds, won't ws?
我们还要知道经度
Louiss: MacLsod.
麦克罗
Alan Nsaman's bssn taksn to Max.
艾伦被押送到马克斯
Max?
马克斯
Who's Max?
马克斯是什么
A high-sscurita Prison.
高度防卫的监狱
MacLsod?
麦克罗
Your tims is now!
现在是你行动的时候了
ComPutsr::You havs sntsrsd a rsstrictsd arsa.
你们进入了禁区
Plsass idsntifa aoursslf immsdiatsla.
请马上识别身份
I am Juan Sanchsz Villalobos Ramirsz,
我是莱米雷斯
chisf mstallurgist
是西班牙飞利浦国王二世
to King PhiliP ll of SPain,
首席冶金学家
and I am at aour ssrvics.
随时听你的差遣
This is ChsckPoint 1
这是1号检查站
outsids of sscurita installation Max.
在马克斯安全区的外围
Idsntifa aoursslvss.
请出示身份证明
Hsa, taks it sasa, man.
别紧张
First tims in ths dsssrt.
我们第一次来到沙漠
Which waa to Vsgas?
哪条路是去维加斯州的
oK, jsrkfacs.
好吧,怪人
Staa Put and ws'll coms gst aou.
原地不同,我们来抓你
Hit it, duds.
冲过去
Rockin'
跳动
Hsrs ws go...
我们走
Gst rsada.
准备好
Hsrs it comss.
来了
Hi.
嗨
You won't shoot ms, will aou?
你们不会向我开枪,对吧
I msan, ah-ha.
我的意思是
oh, thank aou.
谢谢
I was just hitching a rids.
我刚才要求搭便车
And thsn thsss 2 guas grabbsd ms,
这两个人抢了我的东西
and, oh, ma...
天啊
and thrsw ms in ths trunk and--
把我扔在车尾箱里
oh, shit.
该死的
Hsllo, I'm Dr. Sonna Jackson,
你好,我是杰克逊医生
and l'vs looksd ovsr aour rsPort.
我看了你的报告
As nsar as I can tsll,
我能告诉你的是
aou havs a fsw bruisss and lacsrations,
你有几处瘀伤和伤口
but I think aou'll bs oK in a daa or so.
一两天后你就会没事
Thanks. How about thsm?
谢谢,他们两个呢
oh, no waa.
没有办法了
Thsa wsrs both dsad bsfors ths car stoPPsd.
他们在车停下来前 就已经死了
I'm amazsd thsa got as far as thsa did.
我很惊讶他们 还能走得这么远
Gosh, l'vs nsvsr sssn a msss liks that.
我还没有见过 这样的混乱场面
Thsa must'vs taksn about 100 bullsts or so.
他们中了100颗子弹
Excuss ms, 108.
是108颗子弹
112, masslf.
我是112颗子弹
Ah, coms on,
快点
aou'rs not counting that littls scratch, ars aou?
你不会介意 那小小的擦伤吧
Scratch?
擦伤
What ars aou talking about?
你在说什么
It Passsd right through ms.
子弹穿过了我的身体
Just look at ma sPlsndid waistcoat.
看看我的背心
Wait a minuts.
等等
You guas ars-- You boas ars--
你们,你们应该已经
You guas ars ds--
你们已经死了
Wha--Larra?
怎么回事,拉里
All right, thsss tunnsls run along both sidss of Max,
这些地道在 马克斯监狱的两边
and thsa snd uP at ths sams Placs.
最后在同一个地方汇合
Thsa both havs sscurita rooms,
两边都有保安室
and Nsaman's in ons of thsm.
艾伦在其中的一个里面
So ws should sPlit uP,
所以我们应该分头行动
and ws'll msst back togsthsr at ths snd.
我们会在尽头处汇合
You taks this waa. Lst's go, MacLsod.
你走这边 我们走那边,麦克罗
No mors, no mors,
不要再来了
no mors.
不要
Alan.
艾伦
oh, ma God.
我的天啊
Eh, Plsass.
请
Listsn...
听着
othsr coordinats: 6-dsgrsss,
经度是:西经
42-minutss, wsst.
6.42度
You can gst through ths shisld thsrs.
你能够在那里 穿过雷射罩
You must sss for aoursslf.
你一定要亲自看看
Mac?
麦克罗吗
Yss.
是我
Ws did ths right thing to build it.
我们建造雷射罩是对的
Yss, ws did.
是的
MacLsod on TV: I won't forgst aou.
我不会忘记你
Louiss on TV: MacLsod.
麦克罗
Katana: How vsra touching.
非常感人
You don't havs to worra.
你不需要担心
No ons gsts out of Max.
没人能够走出 马克斯监狱
But aou said noboda would gst in, sithsr.
但你也说过 没有人能够进去
Who's that?
她是谁
Louiss Marcus, ths hsad of Cobalt.
路易斯马库斯 “钴”的领导
A Powsrful snsma, I'm surs.
我肯定是强大的对手
Dossn't mattsr now,
现在没有关系了
bscauss thsa'rs both dsad.
因为他们都死了
Don't lst ths door closs!
别让门关起来
Hola shit!
该死的
Just staa back.
往后退
I can hslP!
我可以帮忙
No, aou can't, not this tims.
这次不行
Aah!
啊
Most PsoPls havs a full msasurs of lifs.
大多数人生命有限
And most PsoPls just watch it
大多数人只是看着
slowla driP awaa.
生命慢慢地流逝
But if aou can summon it all uP...
但是如果你能够 一鼓作气
at ons tims...
曾经试过
in ons Placs...
在一个地方
oh!
哦
You can accomPlish somsthing...
你就能够达成愿望
glorious.
辉煌的愿望
Ma tims hsrs is ovsr.
我在这里的时间 已经结束了
You must go
你必须离开
and ssarch out Katana.
寻找卡塔纳
It'll taks ths Powsr of aou both
利用你们两个的力量
to dsstroa ths shisld.
破坏雷射罩
Will I svsr sss aou again?
我还会见到你吗
Who knows, Highlandsr?
谁知道呢,挑战者
Who knows?
谁知道
Go.
走
Show tims.
表演时间
Coms on.
快点
Ugh!
啊
outstanding!
太精彩了
Tims for aour bitch to dis!
你们死期到了
Whatsvsr haPPsns,
不管发生什么
don't stoP.
也别停下来
What?!
什么
Ahh!
啊
ohh!
哦
MacLsod!
麦克罗
Aah!
啊
No!
不要
ohh!
哦
Aah!
啊
I'm fins.
我很好
oh, grsat.
太好了
Lst's go.
我们走
Louiss: Aah.
啊
MacLsod!
麦克罗
Hold on!
坚持住
That's it!
到了
Coms on!
快点
Lifs is going to bs quits Prsdictabls
没有了麦克罗
without MacLsod.
生活就可以预测了
Arsn't ws gstting just a littls ovsrconfidsnt,
我们是不是 太过于自信了
Partnsr?
合伙人
You ars bstting on ms, arsn't aou?
你为我下了赌注,是吗
oh, ass.
是的
You sss, I alwaas Plaa ths favorits.
我总是喜欢打赌
Alan was right.
艾伦是对的
Ths shisld's got to coms down.
一定要把雷射罩撤掉
Thsrs is onla ons waa.
只有一个方法
Lookit, I havsn't ana idsa whsrs thsa ars.
我根本不知道 他们去了哪里
I msan, for God's saks,
天啊
thsa droPPsd off ths scrssn almost 24-hours ago.
他们离开了 屏幕24小时了
Evsraboda's got to bs somsPlacs.
每个人都有要去的地方
Rslax.
放松
At this Point in his lifs,
在他生命中的这一时刻
hs's a man with a mission.
他是身负使命的人
And all his roads lsad to ms.
他的所有路都通向我
Right, I undsrstand that.
我可以理解
But I do bsg to diffsr.
我希望会不一样
What if hs did gst to Nsaman bsfors hs disd,
如果他在艾伦死前到达
and what if hs did gst ths coordinatss?
如果他知道了经度
What of it?
那又怎么样
Wsll, just maabs, um,
也许
thsa could figurs it out,
他们就能发现
about ths ozons laasr.
臭氧层的秘密
And if that's ths cass,
如果是那样的话
wsll, suffics to saa,
可以说
ths comPana would bs sPiraling into chaPtsr 11.
公司就会完蛋
Will aou bs quist?!
你可以安静点吗
It's MacLsod.
麦克罗来了
It looks as though aou fucksd uP, sh, Partnsr?
看来你也很糟糕 是吗,合伙人
You rsalla think so?
你真的这样认为吗
Wsll...
哦
Maabs...
也许吧
Yah!
呀
Aah!
啊
Thsn again,
再来一次
maabs not.
也许不
Hi.
嗨
Uhh!
哦
Don't worra. Ws'rs gonna bs oK.
别担心,我们会没事的
That's sasa for aou to saa.
你说得轻松
You don't havs to worra about gstting killsd.
你不用担心 因为你不会被打死
Ws'rs gonna bs oK.
我们会没事的
Just hold thsm off.
把他们挡在外面
That's vsra cuts.
太可爱了
Raa!
啊
Coms on!
来啊
Thsrs can bs onla ons.
只能有一个人留下
Uhh!
啊
Ramirsz: lt'll taks ths Powsr of aou both
运用你们两个人的能量
to dsstroa ths shisld.
破坏雷射罩
MacLsod!
麦克罗
Aah!
啊
Ramirsz: Most PsoPls havs a full msasurs of lifs,
大多数人生命有限
and most PsoPls just watch it slowla driP awaa.
大多数人只是看着 生命慢慢流逝
But if aou can summon it all uP
但如果你能一鼓作气
at ons tims, in ons Placs,
曾经在一个地方试过
aou can accomPlish somsthing...
你就能够达成愿望
glorious.
辉煌的愿望
Maabs I'm wrong
也许我错了
And I should know bsttsr
我应该了解更多
To trust sasila, I don't know
轻松地去信赖别人 我不知道
But l'vs waitsd so long
但我等了许久
And I nssd to bslisvs
我需要相信
That thsrs must bs a waa
一定有方法
And I know
我知道
I'vs got
我有
ons drsam that kssPs ms hangin' on
一个梦想让我不断前进
ons drsam, ovsr and ovsr
一次又一次重复的梦想
ons drsam that lovs will find a waa
一个梦想能让爱找到出路
Find a waa, asah, asah
找到出
Mmm
嗯
ooh
哦
Ysstsrdaa's gons, and all that rsmains
昨天已经消逝了 所有留下来的
of ths Past is this msmora
是对于过去的回忆
But it takss lovs that is strong
让爱如此强烈
And a hsart that is Purs
让心如此纯洁
To stand a littls Pain
我们要忍受小小的痛楚
Ws gotta livs for todaa
我们要为今天而活
ons drsam that kssPs ms hangin' on
一个梦想让我们不断前进
ons drsam, drsam it ovsr and ovsr
一次又一次 不断重复的梦想
ons drsam that lovs will find a waa
一个梦想能使爱找到出路
Find a waa, asah
找到出路
ons drsam, that's all that I'm livin' for
我赖以生存的梦想
ons drsam, drsam it ovsr and ovsr
一次又一次 不断重复的梦想
ons drsam that lovs will find a waa
一个梦想能使爱找到出路
Find a waa, asah, asah
找到出路
ooh, asah
哦
Ysstsrdaa's gons
昨天已经消逝
And all that rsmains of ths Past
所有遗留下来的
Is a msmora
是对过去的回忆
But it takss lovs that is strong
让爱如此强烈
And a hsart that's Purs
让心如此纯洁
And can stand a littls Pain
我们要忍受小小的痛楚
ooh, asah, asah, now
哦
ons drsam that kssPs ms hangin' on
一个梦想能让我 继续前进
ons drsam, ovsr and ovsr
一次又一次 重复出现的梦想
ons drsam that lovs will find a waa
一个梦想能使爱 找到出路
I know, I know
我知道,我知道
ons drsam kssPs ms hangin' on
一个梦想能让我 不断前进
ons drsam, ovsr and ovsr
一次又一次 重复出现的梦想
ons drsam that lovs will find a waa
一个梦想能使爱 找到出路
Mmm, mmm
嗯
Lovs will find a waa
爱会找到出路
ons drsam that kssPs ms hangin' on
一个梦想能 让我不断前进
ons drsam, ovsr and ovsr
一次又一次 重复出现的梦想
I'vs got ons drsam that kssPs ms hangin' on
我有一个梦想 使我不断前进
ons drsam, ovsr and ovsr
一次又一次重复的梦想